Chuck Zapata

14 years of Hospitality experience. Im professional, dependable and experienced. Extensive knowledge in the daily operations of a Hotel and a commitment to meeting and exceeding guests needs. Hard working and excellent team player and communicator. Computer literate, experienced in using property management systems.

Horsham, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Chuck-Zapata/14e3871e2b70d39e

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Head Engineer/ Maintenance Manager

Days Inn Hotel - Horsham, PA - 2010 to 2013

Chief Engineer (2010-2013) Maintenance (2006-2010)

- Daily preventive Maintenance for 171 guest room property
- Painting, plumbing, electrical, drywall, flooring, equipment cleaning, furniture repairs, electronic room key system repairs
- Daily maintenance of public/employee areas interior/exterior of hotel, ordering supplies
- · Interviewing, hiring staff, training and scheduling
- · Keeping and improving records, checklists, and reports on file

Front Desk Manager

Days Inn Hotel - Horsham, PA - 2004 to 2006

Scheduling, training, staffing for front desk

- Held weekly meetings to keep staff and Mngmt. up to date and on same page
- Handled guest concerns and Questions daily
- Booked reservations, checked guests in/out, handled room accounts
- Created daily checklists for AM and PM shifts at front desk

Night Auditor

Days Inn Hotel - Horsham, PA - 2003 to 2004

Ran Daily reports, processed CC transactions, closed out day in system

- · Handled all front desk duties overnight also setup continental breakfast daily
- Checked and maintained public areas for preventive and security issues

clerk

Front Desk - 2000 to 2003

Booked reservations, handled guests check ins /outs, guests needs and requests

 Processed arrivals/departures/payments/competitor rate checks/ handled cash drawer/ answered phones/ coordinated with other departments/put together guest gift bags/guest courtesy calls

EDUCATION

High school or equivalent

Hatboro Horsham High School 1996 to 2000

SKILLS

hotel experience, hotel experience (10+ years), Customer Service (10+ years)